你居然没告诉我  我们还是夫妻
l cannot believe that you didn't tell me we are still married!
-我本打算告诉你  -什么时候啊
- Look, l was going to tell you. - When?
在我们第一个秘密孩子出生后吗
After the birth of our first secret child?
罗斯没办注销
Ross didn't get the annulment.
我们还是夫妻
We are still married!
-什么  不是吧  -我的天啊
- What? You're kidding. - Oh, my God!
-罗斯  -或许这个决定不好
-Ross. - lt wasn't my best decision,
但我无法面对另一次失败的婚姻
but l couldn't face another failed marriage.
好吧  我打断问一句
Okay, I need to drop in and ask.
你觉得这段婚姻哪里成功了
At what point did you think this was a successful marriage?
瑞秋  别这样
Rach, come on.
其实想想  还蛮有意思的
lf you think about it, it's actually kind of funny.
好吧  还是不要想好了
Okay, maybe it's best not to think about it.
这真是不可原谅
Okay, his is inexcusable.
我真是震惊到极点
l'm shocked to my very core.
菲比  我已经告诉她你知道了
Phoebe, l told her you already knew.
又在骗人  你这是病啊
Another lie. You have a sickness!
罗斯  我在想
Ross, fcor my own peace of mind,
你没娶我们其他人吧
are you married to any more of us? Are you?
我的鞋
My shoe!
你居然掉了一只鞋在这里啊
You left a shoe here?
我回到家才发现的
l didn't realize till l got home.
你让我当时光一只脚走回来拿吗
l wasn't gonna walk all the way back down here with one shoe.
我要去找那个人的车
You know what? l'll go find that guy's car
然后在挡风玻璃上留张条
and leave a note on the windshield.
他回来找钥匙的时候
When he comes back for his keys,
我会把你的鞋子交给他
l'll make sure to give him your shoe.
好的  谢谢
Great. Thanks.
太好了  你们在这里  听着
Oh, good. You guys are here. Listen.
明天要不要一起
How would you like to spend tomorrow
照顾三只超可爱的小狗
taking care of three incredible cute little puppies?
天啊  肯定很有趣  听起来不错
My God! What a fun day! That sounds great!
好吧
Yeah, all right.
好的  那我明早带它们过来
Okay, l'll bring them by tomorrow morning.
对了  跟你说一下  它们不是真的小狗
Okay, by the way, they're not actually puppies.
是弗兰克和爱丽丝的三胞胎  再见
They're Frank and Alice's triplets. Okay, see you.
什么
What?
拜托拜托拜托  求求你们了
Please, please, please. Oh, please, please?
弗兰克和爱丽丝托我带三胞胎
Frank and Alice...asked me to baby-sit the triplets.
我好紧张  我从没单独带过孩子
l'm nervous. 'Cause l've never done that before by myself.
放心  我们一定会帮忙
Don't worry. We'll absolutely do it.
那我就算了吧
Yeah, l'm gonna pass,
你开始说是狗狗时  我就很犹豫了
because l was kind of iffy when it was puppies.
好啦  钱德勒  好嘛
Come on, Chandler, come on.
这可是个练习的好机会  以免...
lt'll give us great practice for when...
有客人带了孩子来家里
...people with babies come to visit.
-好车  -是啊  不是我的
- Nice car. - Yeah, it's not mine.
-我喜欢你的车  -是啊  它是...我的
- l love your car. - Yeah, it's mine.
-一定很猛  -我也是
- l bet it's fast. - Me too. Yeah.
而且很舒服
And comfortable.
-你喜欢皮革座椅吗  -当然了
- Do you like leather seats? - Yeah.
它正好有
lt's got them!
我还有东西在这里
So l still have boxes here.
也有东西在罗斯家
l still have boxes at Ross's .
而我却没地方住
And l have nowhere to live.
我理智线随时能断呢
l could so easily freak out right now.
那我呢
What about me?
我刚知道狄妮丝要出远门
I just found out Denise is leaving town for a while.
我没室友了
l don't have a roommate.
也许我可以当你的室友  菲比
Well, maybe l could be your roommate, Pheebs.
也对  你可以当我室友
Maybe you could be my roommate!
这主意不错
Well, there's an idea!
太好了
That would be great!
狄妮丝要去多久
How long is Denise gone for?
她说她12月26日回来
She said she'd be back December 26th.
12月26日
December 26th.
也许她是圣诞老公公
Maybe she's Santa Claus.
看谁来了
Oh, look who it is.
我老公  我的心肝宝贝
My husband, the apple of my eye.
我已经约好明天两点上庭
Okay, l got us a court date for tomorrow at 2...
表格也都拿全了
...and l picked up all the forms.
我会全部搞定的
l'll take care of everything.
当然  你都说你会全部搞定
Sure, if you say you'll take care of everything,
我"当然"没理由怀疑你
l have no reason to doubt you.
把表都给我
Give me those forms.
我要照我的方式去做
l'm gonna do this my way
你不准叽叽歪歪
and l don't wanna hear a peep out of you.
-好  瑞秋  但是...  -你在叽叽歪歪喔
- Okay, Rach, but--  - You're peeping!
罗斯  我实在是
Ross, you know what? l just got--
-你为什么要这样  -我说过...
- Why did you do this? - l told you- -
我不想听"三次失败的婚姻"的屁话
l don't wanna hear "three failed marriages."
如果你失败过两次  就会了解了
Look if you'd had two failed marriages, you'd understand.
多亏你  我现在只差一次了
Well, you know what? Thanks to you, l'm halfway there.
我要气炸了  罗斯
Oh, l am so mad, Ross!
我从来没有这么生气过
l don't think l've ever been this angry!
那我说我们分手了的那次呢
What about when l said we were on a break?
菲比  情况如何
Pheebs, how's it going?
我还好  进展挺顺利的
l'm doing okay. I think it's going well.
你觉得他们开心吗
Do you think they having fun?
我讲话太快了吗
Am l talking too fast?
不会  跟我差不多
No. You sound like me.
一切都很好
lt's going great.
你看钱德勒和小女生钱德勒
Look at Chandler with Little Baby Girl Chandler.
小女生钱德勒
Little Baby Girl Chandler.
听起来好熟啊  谁这么叫过我
Where have l heard that before?
对  鲁宾教练
Oh, Coach Rubin.
菲比  等你那边忙完
You know what? Pheebs, when you're done over there,
我这里也出了点状况
we've got a kind of situation over here too.
不行  我们各自负责自己的宝宝
No. We are all responsible for our own babies.
瞧  你这么说就不对了
See? That's where you're wrong.
我们不应该一对一地防守这些娃娃
We've been playing the babies man-to-man.
我们应该尝试区域联防
We should really be playing a zone defense.
-什么意思  -如果我们各自负责一个区域
- What do you mean? - I just think things'll go a lot smoother
事情会顺利很多
if we each have a zone, you know.
菲比  你可以负责给他们擦洗
Phoebe, be in charge of wiping.
莫妮卡  负责给他们换尿布
And Mon, be in charge of diapering.
我则可以负责欣赏
l'll be in charge of looking at how cute they are
他们那可爱的小模样
when they put their hands....
听起来不错
That sounds great,
但怎么不是你负责给他们擦洗
but you should be in charge of wiping.
我是个新手
Okay, l'm a rookie.
难以承担如此大任
l should not be in the end zone.
这太有意思了
This is so great.
我们餐厅里就是这样摆盘子的
This is exactly how we set the plates at the restaurant.
是吗   可这不是我点的菜啊
Yeah? Well, this is not what l ordered.
大家好
Hey, guys.
宝宝们好
Hey, babies.
今早超级开心
l'm having the best morning.
那辆我有钥匙的保时捷   还在那儿呢
That Porsche l've got the keys to? Still there.
太"意外"了  因为钥匙在你手上嘛
Shocking, since you still have the keys.
我在车旁时  别人对我的那个态度啊
You should see the treatment l get when I was with that car.
每个人都很友善  找我聊天
People are friendly. They wanna talk.
而且不只是聊车子
And not just about the car.
还有人给我的股票投资提建议
One guy advised me on my equity investments.
什么股票投资
What equity investments?
赚到保时捷的那支股票投资嘛
The ones that got me the Porsche.
用心听好吗
Will you keep up?
要是他们看到我总是白站着
lf people keep seeing me just standing there,
他们就会怀疑那不是我的车了
they're gonna start to think l don't own it.
所以我就去个洗车吧
So l figure l'll wash it, right?
莫妮卡  能借我水桶和肥皂吗
Monica, you got a bucket and soap I could borrow?
有  我有肥皂  海绵  抹布
Oh, yeah. l got soap and sponges and rags...
亮光腊和打腊工具组
...and carnauba wax and polishing compound.
你根本没有车
You don't even have a car.
对啊  但有次楼下停了一辆很脏的车
l know. Once there was a dirty car in front of the building,
我就把它给洗了
so l washed it.
-还有呢  -还有另外六辆
- And? - And six others.
果然
There you are.
对  它可以飙到130英里
Yeah, she tops out at 130.
这还是在市区
That's just in the city.
郊外公路可以上到160英里呢
l get her up to 160 when take her to upstate.
是吗   你在郊外有房子啊
Really? You got a place upstate?
当然
Sure.
-改天见  -好  慢走
- All right. See you later. - Okay. Take it easy.
喂   那是我的车
Hey. That's my car.
是吗
Really?
再给我五分钟
Just give me five more minutes.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我捡到钥匙
l found the keys
现在在帮它打腊
and now l'm just polishing her up.
-但这是我的车  -但这是我的腊
- But it's my car. - Yeah, but it's my wax.
听着  我很少进市区
Listen, l don't come to the city much.
我不知道你是疯子
l don't know if you're crazy
还是在演什么街头剧  但...
or if this is some street theater, but...
可以把钥匙还给我吗
could l have my keys?
拿去  我会帮你占这车位
Sure. Yeah. l'll save your parking spot.
我不回来了
l'm not coming back.
为什么  我住在郊外
- Why not? - l live upstate.
是啊  我本来也是
Yeah, so did l.
我之前不知道在紧张什么
l don't know why l was so nervous. about this..
也不明白法兰克他们为什么总是抱怨
and why Frank and Alice are always complaining.
-带孩子太容易了  -是啊  两小时和一辈子
- This is so easy. - Yeah, two hours, a lifetime,
是一样的
that's the same.
你们看
Check it out! Check it out!
宝宝醒来后
When the babies wake up...
就能跟克罗格玩啦
...they can meet Krog!
钱德勒  你在干嘛
Chandler, what are you doing?
那东西会把人的眼睛弄瞎的
That thing could put someone's eye out.
他比这能耐多了  他还能毁灭宇宙
He can do more than that. He can destroy the universe.
钱德勒  宝宝可能会误食小零件
No,  Chandler, they could swallow one of those little parts.
再看看他那一个部位
Also, look at his smooth area.
对他们心灵会造成不良影响的
That's just gonna mess them up.
他们才不会误食什么
They are not gonna swallow anything.
你们也太保护过度了吧
You guys are being way too overprotective.
我小时候  我妈都把我
When l was a kid, my mom used to
扔在碎玻璃堆里
throw me into a pile of broken glass.
-什么  -玻璃  沙子  还不都一样嘛
- What? - Glass, sand, whatever.
看  小莱丝莉边睡边伸懒腰
Look at little Leslie stretching in her sleep.
好可爱喔
Oh, it's so cute.
我好奇你是从几岁之后
I wonder what age it is when you stop
才不能把腿举到头上的
being able to both legs behind your head.
我现在还可以
l can still do that.
那你怎么会到现在还没男朋友呢
How are you still single?
好的
All right.
我想或许你们说得对
l thought about it and maybe you're right.
克罗格可能不是个安全的玩具
Maybe Krog is not a safe toy.
知道就好  你为什么改口了
Good. What made you change your mind?
我吞了他的音速爆破枪
l swallowed his sonic blaster gun.
怎么会这样
How did that happen?
我想证明我是对的
l was trying to prove that l was right, you know.
结果证实我错了
And it turns out l was wrong...
现在它卡在我的喉咙了
...and now it's lodged in my throat.
糟糕  我们这两小时
Damn it! Y'know this whole time
光顾着带小孩
we were concentrating on the babies...
都忘了要照看大孩钱德勒了
...and no one was watching Chandler!
两位要申请注销婚姻  是吗
Okay, you are asking the court for an annulment?
是的  法官大人  申请表都填好了
Yes, Your Honor. Here are our forms, all filled out.
根据申请书所言
So based on your petition...
你申请注销的理由是
...you are seeking an annulment on the grounds...
"盖勒先生的精神状况不稳定"
...that "Mr. Geller is mentally unstable."
是  我精神状况不稳定
Fine. l'm mentally unstable.
另外一个理由是
And based on the fact that
"盖勒先生使用静脉注射毒品"
"Mr. Geller is an intravenous drug user."
-什么  -是的  海洛因与可卡因
- What? - Yes. Heroin and crack.
可卡因根本不是静脉注射毒品
Crack isn't even an intravenous drug.
你当然懂啊
Well, you would know.
这上面还说
Now, it also says here that you...
"你在婚前隐瞒性取向"
..."lied about your sexual preference before marriage."
拜托
Oh, come on.
罗斯  我都发现那些杂志了
Ross, please. l found the magazines.
还有你"无法履行夫妻间的义务"
And finally, that you were "unable to consummate the marriage."
这也难怪  你既是同性恋
Well, that makes sense since you're gay
又是瘾君子
and addicted to heroin.
够了  抱歉  这太夸张了
Okay, you know, l'm sorry, this is insane.
我既不是瘾君子
l'm not addicted to heroin,
也不是同性恋  而且...
l'm not gay and there is no problem...
我绝对有能力履行任何"事情"
...with my ability to consummate anything.
我此时此刻就能履行夫妻间的义务
l'll consummate this marriage right here, right now!
没有这个必要
That won't be necessary.
我们交往时
And when we were dating,
简直就像干柴遇上烈火
we consummated like bunnies.
如果你们曾经认真交往过
Now if you two were involved in a serious relationship,
-这事就不好办了  -罗斯  法官大人
- that really creates a problem. - Ross! Your honor,
请放心  我们两年前就分手了
Rest assured, that relationship ended two years ago.
可以删掉"干柴遇上烈火"那句吗
And could you strike "consummated like bunnies" from the record.
这份申请书有任何真话吗
ls there anything in this record that is actually true?
有  我们确实是在拉斯维加斯结的婚
Well, yes. We got married in Vegas.
名字应该也没错
And the names, l think.
从刚才的话听来
Well, based on what l've heard,
你们两位不符合注销资格
you two certainly don't qualify for an annulment.
如果你们不想在一起
lf you don't wanna be together,
就必须办理离婚手续
you'll have to file for divorce.
太好了  你现在高兴了吗
That's great. You happy now?
都是你的搞笑表格害的
Look what you did with your funny, funny form.
什么  是我的错吗
What? Me?
那你那句"干柴遇上烈火"就没有错吗
What about you and your "consummated like bunnies" nonsense?
那...  你在打什么呢
What are you typing that for?
她说我们不能办注销了
She said we don't get the annulment.
不要打
Don't type that. What- -
别再打了
Stop typing!
"别打了   别打了"
"Stop typing, stop typing!"
看见了吧  你居然还不让我跟他离婚
Okay, do you see what you're keeping me married to?
请两位离开我的办公室
You need to get out of my chambers.
好  你给我听着
Look, lady, here's the deal.
我是来办注销的
l came here for an annulment
没办成我绝对不走
and l'm not leaving here until l get one!
你们想在牢里过夜吗
Would you like a night in jail?
耽误您了
Thank you for your time.
保时捷的主人把车开走了
That Porsche guy took his car back.
但你捡到了他的衣橱钥匙吗
But you found the keys to his clothes?
不是  我只是喜欢
No, l just love the way it feels
大家误以为我有保时捷的感觉
when everybody thinks l own a Porsche.
别人会因为你穿着这样
And people will think you own a Porsche
-而觉得你有保时捷吗  -当然会啦
- because you're wearing the clothes? - Of Course!
只有白痴才会没车  还穿成这样
Only an idiot would wear this stuff if he didn't have the car.
那倒是
That is true.
不过只有天才才会误食音速爆破枪
Yeah, but only a genius would swallow a sonic blaster gun.
我也误食过
Oh, l've been there.
我要去开我的保时捷了
l am gonna go drive my Porsche.
乔伊  你知道你没有保时捷吧
Joey, you know you don't actually have one.
你干嘛戳穿我  我正在入戏呢
Come on, what are you doing? l'm in character.
你说说她  好吗
Will you talk to her?
我觉得那玩意儿换位置了  疼死我了
l think it just moved. lt's poking me.
好吧  够了  我们去挂急诊吧
All right, that's it, we're going to the emergency room.
不  你不能把宝宝都留给我一个人照顾
No, you can't leave me here with them.
我们正在带孩子呢
We're babysitting.
宝宝都睡了
The babies are asleep.
你自己撑一下一定没问题
I'm sure you'll be okay on your own.
但你不能把他们都扔给我啊
But you can't leave me with them.
我们可是一个团队
We're a team.
我们在打区域联防  他们会三打一欺负我
We're playing a zone. They'll triple-team me!
他的喉咙卡了个塑胶玩具
He's got something plastic lodged in his throat,
我们非去医院不可
we've got to go to the hospital.
但医生也帮不了他
But a doctor won't be able to help him.
反正过个七年
And it's just gonna...you know,
塑料就会自动降解了
...naturally pass through his system in seven years.
-那说的是口香糖吧  -我确定是枪
- l think that's gum. - l'm pretty sure it's gun.
-真的很痛  我们走吧  -不行
- Okay, listen this really hurts. Let's go. - But no!
男子汉才不会冲去医院
A real man wouldn't just run to the hospital.
别啊  想想克罗格会怎么做
No! What would...what would Krog do?
泊车小弟怎么还没把我的保时捷开来
Why isn't that valet back with my Porsche?
也许因为钥匙在你手上
Maybe because you've got the keys?
全都是你的错
That was totally your fault.
这能怪我吗  你还威胁法官了呢
My fault? You threatened the judge.
你把书记员的打字纸撕下来
You ripped the paper out of the court reporter's machine!
这是唯一能阻止他打字的方法
That was the only way l could get him to stop typing!
你们好啊  盖勒夫妇
Hi. How are the Gellers?
不准叫我们那样
Don't call us that.
法官不准我们办注销
The judge wouldn't let us get an annulment.
现在我们唯有办离婚手续
Now we gotta get a divorce!
你这是被保时捷附身了吗
Did a Porsche throw up on you?
是念保时"皆"
lt's "Porsche- a" !
我完全可以照顾你们  对吧
Me taking care of you is no problem, huh?
你们觉得很安心  对吧
You guys feel safe, right?
我就当你口吐泡泡是同意的意思
l'm gonna take that spit bubble as a "Yeah, l do!"
好的  等我扔了脏尿布  莱斯利
Okay, after I get rid of this dirty diaper, Leslie.
就帮你换一块干净的哦
l'll set you up with a nice clean one.
抱歉
Okay, l'm sorry.
我不是故意吓哭你的  我得先清理一下
l didn't mean to scare you. l just have to clean that up, okay?
因为这是莫妮卡的家
Because, let's face it, we're at Monica's.
摔烂了  好吧
l broke it. All right.
反正东西迟早都会坏
Well, that's just the way things go.
好  就这样
Okay. Good.
为什么只剩两个
Why are there only two of you?
莱斯利呢
Where's Leslie?
对哦  你们不能回答
Well, you can't answer.
莱斯利  你在哪里
Leslie? Where are you, Leslie?
莱斯利  现在是开口说话的好时机
Leslie? Now would be a good time for your first words.
你看看你
Well, look at you!
你有点调皮喔  真是的
You are a little bit mischievous. My gosh!
还"调皮"了不少出来
Oh, you're a lot mischievous.
算了  会干的
Well, it'll dry.
快去跟哥哥妹妹躺在一起...
You sit with your brother and sister now...
他们人呢
...who aren't there.
你还好吗
How do you feel?
克罗格在十二到十四个小时内
Well, let's just say that Krog will be fully equipped to
又能恢复武装
destroy the universe again...
毁灭地球了
...in 12 to 14 hours.
我一个人把孩子都带好了
Okay, l totally took care of the babies all by myself.
喂奶  洗澡  哄他们睡觉
l fed them, bathed them and put them to bed.
还保护他们躲过龙卷风了吗
And protected them from a tornado?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
对啊  宝宝都睡了
l know. The babies are asleep.
菲比  这里发生什么了
Phoebe, what happened here?
我做到了  我一个人照顾宝宝
l did it. l took care of the babies all by myself.
可我的房子
But my apartment!
是菲比胜利的战场
Was the setting of Phoebe's triumph.
可这一团乱
But the mess!
这和菲比独自
ls not as important as the fact that
照看孩子的辛劳相比  实在不算什么
Phoebe took care of the babies all by herself.
好吧
Right.
你说得对  我不该大惊小怪
You're right. l shouldn't freak out.
等我们有了孩子也会这样
This is what it'll be like when we have babies.
那会是什么时候呢
When's that?
菲比  你看你弄得多乱
Phoebe, would you take a look at this mess!
亲爱的  你总算回来了
Oh, honey. Thank God you're home.
我都开始担心了
l was getting worried.
我去领了离婚证书
l picked up the divorce papers.
该签的我都签了
l've already signed everything.
你要签的地方我都画了叉
l put little X's where you need to sign.
还画叉叉呀  真好
Little X's. Great!
这样就能将功赎过了
That makes up for everything.
老实说
You know,
你也干过很多蠢事  好吗
you've done a lot of stupid stuff too, okay?
有哪一件跟这次一样蠢
Name one stupid thing that is as stupid as this one.
你飞去伦敦阻止我结婚那次呢
How about you flew to London to stop my wedding?
我已经结婚了  你还说你爱我
How about you told me you loved me after l was married.
慢着  那不一样
Wait a minute, that was different.
我做那些事是因为我爱你
l did those things because l was in love with you.
对  没错
Yeah, ight.
你说得对  的确很不一样
You're right. That's very different.
总之赶快签吧
So let's just sign the papers.
干嘛
What?
没事
Nothing.
好了  请签名
Okay, can we just sign, please?
恭喜你
Congratulations.
罗斯  等一下
Okay, wait, Ross. Wait a minute.
我有件事要坦白
l kind of have a little confession.
什么事
What?
结婚这件事
Well, you know, this whole marriage thing.
算是我的主意
Kind of my idea.
你说什么
Excuse me?
还记得我们醉得
Remember how we were too drunk
什么都想不起来了吗
to remember anything when we were married?
虽然我不是很想说
l didn't really wanna say anything,
但现在我开始一点点想起来了
but it just kind of kept coming back to me.
还记得我们当时在赌城  你突然
And umm, remember we were in the casino and for some reason,
觉得狂吃葡萄会很好玩吗
you thought it would be funny to eat a lot of grapes.
而我觉得如果我们结婚
And l thought it would be funnier
会更好玩
if we got married.
于是我们折衷
So as a compromise
先去结婚  然后...
we decided first to get married and then...
去吃很多葡萄
...to eat a lot of grapes.
所以我...
So, um...
很抱歉惹出这些麻烦
Sorry l got us into this whole thing.
所以仔细想想
So then, I mean if you think about it...
这一切都是你的错咯
...this is all your fault.
是  不要得寸进尺
Yeah, don't push it, though.
我想说
l gotta say...
我知道我跟很多人离过婚
...l know l divorce a lot of women.
却从来没想过会跟你离婚
Never thought l'd be divorcing you.
我知道
l know.
我总觉得要是我们结婚
l always thought if we got married,
就一定会天长地久
that'd be the one that stuck.
也不会是秘密结婚
And it wouldn't be a secret...
也不会在必胜客吃酒席
...and we wouldn't have our wedding dinner at Pizza Hut.
我有请客吗
Did l even treat?
没有  那是免费的
No, it was on the house.
新婚夫妇  店家招待
lt was a newlywed special.
这真是我听过最凄凉的事了
That may be the most depressing thing l've heard in my life.
我去律师那里送文件
I should probably get these to my lawyer's office.
罗斯  谢谢你把事情都办妥
Thanks, Ross, for taking care of all this.
不客气
No problem.
-我要一份副本  -没问题
- l'm gonna need a copy of those. - Totally.
别在我的保时捷旁边乱跑
Careful around my Porsche!
你好呀  乔伊
Hi, Joey.
你们好呀
Hey. How you doing?
他藏了一辆最拉风的保时捷在下面
He has the most amazing Porsche under there.
我很想给你们看
l'd show you,
但我刚把她哄睡着
but l just tucked her in. She's sleeping.
要不要去跟我喝一杯
Hey uh, would you two girls like to go for a drink?